{
    "subject": "resource/Man_in_the_Moon_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "The film 'Man in the Moon' is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9556972980499268,
            "question": "Is 'Man in the Moon' a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8321835994720459,
            "question": "Who directed 'Man in the Moon'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8003177642822266,
            "question": "Name another film that is similar to 'Man in the Moon'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7413233518600464,
            "question": "Who starred in 'Man in the Moon'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6943250894546509,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'Man in the Moon'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5833044648170471,
            "question": "What type of work is 'Man in the Moon'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43505343794822693,
            "question": "What category does 'Man in the Moon' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30266034603118896,
            "question": "When was 'Man in the Moon' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2818872630596161,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24541784822940826,
            "question": "Give an example of a film."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'Man in the Moon' is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5978_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of a film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5978_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'Man in the Moon' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5978_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What category does 'Man in the Moon' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5978_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5978_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5978_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5978_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5978_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5978_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5978_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5978_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5978_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5978_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5978_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents describe \"The Man In The Moon\" as a film, supporting the statement that it is indeed a type of film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The text does not provide enough information to categorize the film as a specific type of movie, with some passages referring to it as a \"chick flick\" or coming-of-age story but others highlighting its emotional depth and timeless appeal.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}